[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "How do you see this battleground now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Well, clearly you help the vice president to help you get votes to get elected.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "If tax cuts create jobs, what went wrong under President Bush?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Why wouldn't you ideologically want to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Well, yes, ideologically, you would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "You don't agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "OVITZ: Well, it's more of the way -- yes, I don't agree when he says you're not paying your fair share.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Doesn't it depend as much on the individual businesses?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Who you going to vote for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "-- than it has been, 20 years ago, in your experience, since you began making movies?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "I think that it's that whole thing, one step forward, one step back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "What did you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "I said people thought he was Jesus.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "How could that not be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "I agree with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Where do you think if he gets re-elected he should push harder?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "The bottom line is economics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Did you like the Olympics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Say it again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Did you like the Olympics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "You don't see I'm wearing my jacket?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Wasn't bad, was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "You guys did great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "But has it made America more or less racist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, I like to say, first of all, African-Americans alone did not elect President Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Where?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "It was down in Texas I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "How many people die of gunshots in England every year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Well, this is the point I make.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Two, three?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "It averages about 30-odd.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Vulcan"]}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Well what do you do about NRA, which holds this incredible power?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "They got the -- the Vulcan death grip.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Should -- should Barack Obama, rather than just talk in this kind of slightly rhetoric way, as he does about guns, should he now push?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", ":", "MD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "I think they both should.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "It was an amazing moment, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I wanted -- I wanted to hire his speech writer, quite frankly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Is that what you want to see?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "I actually feel totally responsible for where he's at.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Are you nervous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "It scares me, quite frankly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Like 30 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "More than that actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Is there a point to it that could really resonate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I -- my hope would be that it actually -- that society is so receptive to the idea that it doesn't make a point, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "For you as a central player in this, someone that had known Whitney nearly 30 years, singing at the funeral and so on, what was it like for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "RB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "What was your motivation for this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Very important two specific reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "What were the biggest misconceptions about her, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "That she was this difficult diva who lived life in a drug coma, and that, you know, her life at every minute was turmoil.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "People like yourself and the family members who weren't exposed to that kind of things, and other friends perhaps some of them not the most desirable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "Probably.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "I agree that that he wasn't the blame.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Well, it was almost fire and fire, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "To a certain degree, because of just being in the same industry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "Did you ever feel you could have done something to perhaps avert what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "No regrets at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "Why such a patriotic album?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "Because I want to remind through these songs that before any association with any party, we all are Americans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]